

# Nafiz Eren Nasıroğlu

Frontend Developer

+905075675763



🧭 İzmir, Buca



erenasiroglu1@gmail.com



github.com/erenasiroglu



linkedin.com/in/eren-nasiroglu/

## **Profile**

I work with frontend technologies and have in-depth knowledge of tools like React, Redux, Zustand, Vue, and Vuetify. I have experience developing user-friendly interfaces and working on the backend with Node.js. I always write my code following clean code principles and strive to deliver projects to pixel-perfect standards. With my passion for new technologies and constant eagerness to learn, I can bring your projects to life with the highest quality.

# **Professional Experience**

#### 2024/06 - 2024/09 İzmir, Urla Technopark

#### BeforeSunset Al

#### **Software Developer Intern**

- BeforeSunset AI is a project that uses artificial intelligence to help users better plan their time
- In this project, we develop solutions using React, Next.js, Zustand, and Supabase.

#### 2024/09 - Present

#### **Frontend Developer**

#### 2024/03 - 2024/06 İzmir, Menemen ITOB

#### Software Developer (Part-time) **GEMAS Pool Technology**

- Gemas is a company that produces pool technologies.
- In this project, I was involved in creating an e-commerce site using PHP Laravel.
- I developed the frontend of the website and wrote the backend code for the admin panel.

# 2023/05 - 2024/02 İzmir. Urla Technopark

### **Associate Frontend Developer Decktopus Al**

- Decktopus AI is a project that allows users to create presentations quickly using artificial intelligence.
- In this project, I handled feature and bugfix tasks in the frontend using technologies like Vue, Vuetify, GraphQL, and Hasura.
- I created an admin panel for managing customer services.
- I redesigned the signup and login pages.
- I created a channel to manage bugfixes, which helped us take action quickly.
- I facilitated the integration of Google Analytics into the code.

#### 2022/10 - 2023/05

İzmir,

Urla Technopark

# Software Developer Intern Decktopus Al

- Decktopus AI is a startup project that allows users to quickly create presentations using artificial intelligence.
- I completed my internship here and during my internship, I took on tasks in frontend development, data analysis, and software testing.
- I wrote the code using TypeScript.
- For data analysis, I used Python technologies such as NumPy, Matplotlib, and Pandas.
- I was involved in creating the templates used by users and transitioned them through test, staging, and production environments.

### **Educations**

2020/09 - 2024/07

**Izmir** 

Yönetim Bilişim Sistemleri

Izmir Democracy University

2022/02 - 2022/05

Istanbul

Yetkin Gençler MEF University

## **Skills**

React	Redux	SQL	Emotion.js	Next.js	Bitbucket
Vue	GraphQL	Vuetify	Javascript	SCSS	Git
Zustand	Hasura	Tailwind	Figma	Node.js	Data analysis

## **Certificates**

Full Stack Web Development	Advanced Javacript	Website Availability	React
Udemy	Udemy	BTK Akademi	Patika.dev
Advanced Web Development	Akbank Backend	Advanced Javacript	Google GDSC
Advanced Web Development	ARBUIR BUCKCHU	Advanced bavacript	Google GDGG
Udemy	Bootcamp	Udemy	Google
	Akbank		

# **Projects**

**Landing Page** 

github.com/erenasiroglu/landing-page

**Quiz App** 

github.com/erenasiroglu/quiz-app

E-ticaret Websitesi

github.com/erenasiroglu/allthestars

Al Chatbot

github.com/erenasiroglu/chatbot-ollama

File Embedder

github.com/erenasiroglu/langchain-file-embedder

Zaman Sayacı Uygulaması

github.com/erenasiroglu/case-study